(Raj:)Oh, what did I do?
(Howard:)You made us feel like
we're not trying hard enough.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, we were totally fine
half-assing our marriage
(Bernadette:)till you showed up.
(Raj:)Look, I'm sorry
you're upset with me,
(Raj:)but I just have to say
it's nice to see
(Raj:)the two of you on the same page.
(Howard:)Oh, it does feel good
(Howard:)to have you backing me up for once.
-l back you up all the time!
-That is not--
-He's doing it again!
-What is wrong with you?!
(Leonard:)I can't believe they kicked you out.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe
they're still married.
(Raj:)Oh, no, I forgot Cinnamon's
toothbrush at Howards.
(Raj:)I guess you're sharing
with Daddy again.
(Penny:)Bark once if you need me
to call PETA.
(Sheldon:)What's that animal doing
in our apartment?
(Leonard:)Oh, relax, she's in her crate.
She can't get out.
(Sheldon:)Jurassic Park.
(Sheldon:)This day just keeps
getting worse and worse.
(Penny:)You know, if it makes
you feel any better--
(Sheldon:)-It probably won't.
-You're probably right.